

#### Walter A. Jablonowski

Al first developer

walterjab@outlook.com

Am Anger 996135 Stegaurach

PHP

javascript

HTML

CSS

**Python** 

SQL

**DB-Design** 



English: fluent





## **Summary**

25 years of experience in programming with a focus on PHP based web applications since about 10 years, as well as design of databases and plain SQL development. Experience in "AI first" development. Interested in minimalistic solutions and innovative technologies.

# Special skills

Al superpowers: 3-4 times increased productivity through Al usage. Passionate about making minimalistic apps. Many features and components can be replaced with simpler

Read more ...

(i) code samples online is.gd/waj\_cv

### Goals

- "Al first" development and development of Al features
- Ideally working on AI solutions or topic of interest, e.g. nutrition, information management, innovation
- also DB design and plain SQL development
- Part-time 16h (remote)
- Maintain work-life balance with flexible hours





my Al tools ☑

Born: 1978-09-11
Nationality: German
Marital status: single

#### Scan me



# **Experience**

01/2021 - 07/2024 Web developer

Company: VX APPS, Hildesheim

New PHP web application (part-time, home office)

05/2019 - 01/2021 Web developer

**Company**: inixmedia GmbH, Schwentinental New PHP web application (part-time, home office)

09/2015 - 12/2017 Mobile- and web developer

**Company**: Varimetrix Deutschland GmbH, Kummersbrück iOS and Android Apps, new web application based on PHP, js (part-time, home office)

02/2004 - 05/2012 Self-employed

Self-employed software developer / freelancer: Development of apps for iPhone, business applications for Windows, database design, SQL development

### **Education**

09/2000 - 02/2003 CIB, Bamberg

**Degree**: Fachinformatiker Anwendungsentwicklung

09/1989 - 05/1999 Clavius Gymnasium

Degree: Mittlere Reife

powered by cv-maker © Walter A. Jablonowski 2024